; MCM localization
$Spell Options	Spell Options
$Magicka Cost Per Cast (Spell)	Magicka Cost Per Cast (Spell)
$Enchant Charge Per Cast (Staff)	Enchant Charge Per Cast (Staff)
$Experience Per Cast	Experience Per Cast
$Item Notification Spam	Item Notification Spam
$Harvest Food	Harvest Food
$Harvest Hearthfire	Harvest Hearthfire
$Maintenance	Technical
$Recall Active Critters	Recall Active Critters
$Clear Flora Cache	Clear Flora Cache
$Getter Critters	Getter Critters
$Max Concurrent Critters	Max Concurrent Critters
$Spawn Distance Multiplier	Spawn Distance Multiplier
$Critter Return Distance Offset	Critter Return Distance Offset
$Use Green Thumb	Use Green Thumb
$Show Critter Stats	Show Critter Stats
$Delete Getter Critters	Delete Getter Critters
$[Please close menu]	[Please close menu]
$Quest Start Mode	Quest Start Mode
$Story Manager	Story Manager
$Start	Start
$skypal	SkyPal

$OIDcrittercap_INFO	How many Getter Critters can be active at a time.\nThe default value should be fine, but you can try lowering it if you experience game instability while casting.
$OIDrecall_INFO	Immediately returns all active critters to the cache, and attempts to fix any cache errors if present.\nYou can try running this if any critters become stuck, or if the mod generally becomes unresponsive.\nAfter running this, don't cast any Harvest spells until you see the completion notification.
$OIDexp_INFO	How much Alteration exp to award per Getter Critter summon.
$OIDclear_INFO	Clears all examined/learned harvestables, as well as the temporary reference cache.\nRun this if you install a mod that adds or edits harvestables mid-save, or change the food setting above.\nAfter running this, don't cast any Harvest spells until you see the completion notification.
$OIDnspam_INFO	Toggles the "<item> Added" notifications, as well as item pickup sounds that play when a Getter Critter returns.
$OIDgt_INFO	Toggles whether Getter Critters inherit the Green Thumb perk from from the caster, if they have it.\nYou may wish to disable this for balance reasons.
$OIDhf_INFO	Toggles whether the mod will attempt to harvest Hearthfire planters, and anything else using the same system.\nWill NOT work without USSEP 4.2.0+, or the optional "Vanilla Fixes" module.\nNOTE: Changes to this setting will not fully take effect until you also run Clear Flora Cache.
$OIDspawnDist_INFO	Multiplies the distance at which critters will (try to) spawn in front of the caster.\nNegative values will cause critters to spawn behind the caster instead.
$OIDreturnOffset_INFO	Values above zero will control how close critters will AI pathfind back to the caster before despawning.\nThis can help reduce how often critters bump the caster, though AI pathfinding still tends to be unpredictable.\n64 units = 1 yard
$OIDstats_INFO	Show a message box containing recorded mod stats.\nNote that this will not be accurate if run while any critters are active.
$OIDstaffdrain_INFO	Amount of charge to drain from the a Staff of Harvest per critter spawn.\nNote that the staff has a capacity of 4,000.
$OIDmagickadrain_INFO	Amount of magicka to drain per critter spawn.\nNote that Alteration cost reduction is capped at 85% for this spell.
$OIDfood_INFO	Toggles whether the mod will also learn harvestables that produce food, instead of just ingredients.\nNOTE: Changes to this setting will not fully take effect until you also run Clear Flora Cache.
$OIDdelete_INFO	Immediately deletes all spawned critters. If the mod stops working, this may fix it,\nhowever it will also reset stats as shown by the Show Critter Stats button.\nWill also attempt to clean up "dead" critters on the ground.
$OIDquestmode_INFO	Controls which method the mod uses to search for objects.\n"Story Manager" seems stable, but is occasionally unreliable, depending on how busy the engine is.\n"Start" is more reliable, but a related engine bug sometimes freezes the entire game. Not recommended.\n"SkyPal" is a custom SKSE library by doticu that should be the fastest and most reliable, if available.